en:
  get_a_teacher_relocation_payment: &get_a_teacher_relocation_payment
    accessibility_statement:
      test_date: "28 July 2022"
      prepared_date: "31 July 2019"
      updated_date: "28 July 2022"
    journey_name: "Get a teacher relocation payment"
    feedback_email: "international.RELOCATIONPAYMENT@education.gov.uk"
    claim_description: "for a get a teacher relocation payment"
    claim_subject: "International relocation payment"
    support_email_address: "international.RELOCATIONPAYMENT@education.gov.uk"
    forms:
      previous_payment_received:
        question: "Have you previously received an international relocation payment?"
        answers:
          true:
            answer: "Yes"
          false:
            answer: "No"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Select Yes if you have previously received an international relocation payment"
      application_route:
        question: "What is your employment status?"
        hint: "Select one of the following options"
        answers:
          teacher:
            answer: "I am employed as a teacher in a school in England"
          salaried_trainee:
            answer: "I am enrolled on a salaried teacher training course in England"
            hint: "‘Salaried’ means a course where you are paid a wage to work while you train."
          other:
            answer: "Other"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Select the option that applies to you"
      state_funded_secondary_school:
        question: "Are you employed by an English state secondary school?"
        hint:
          "State schools receive funding from the UK government. Secondary schools teach children aged 11 to 16, or 11
          to 18."
        answers:
          true:
            answer: "Yes"
          false:
            answer: "No"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Select the option that applies to you"
      contract_details:
        question: "Are you employed on a contract lasting at least one year?"
        hint: "Your contract can also be ongoing or permanent."
        answers:
          true:
            answer: "Yes"
          false:
            answer: "No"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Select the option that applies to you"
      start_date:
        question: "Enter the start date of your contract"
        errors:
          presence: "Enter your contract start date"
          date_not_in_future: "Start date cannot be in the future"
      subject:
        question: "What subject are you employed to teach at your school?"
        hint:
          "Physics, general or combined science including physics, and languages can be combined with other subjects but
          must make up at least 50% of your time in the classroom."
        answers:
          physics: "Physics"
          combined_with_physics: "General or combined science, including physics"
          languages: "Languages"
          other: "Other"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Choose a subject"
      changed_workplace_or_new_contract:
        question: "Have you changed where you work or started a new contract since you last applied?"
        hint: "This includes any changes since your last application"
        answers:
          true:
            answer: "Yes"
          false:
            answer: "No"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Select yes if you have changed where you work or started a new contract since you last applied"
      breaks_in_employment:
        question: Have you had any breaks in employment during the last 3 academic terms?
        hint: Include any breaks during term time when you were not working
        errors:
          inclusion: Select yes if you have had any breaks in employment during the last 3 academic terms
        answers:
          true:
            answer: "Yes"
          false:
            answer: "No"
      visa:
        question: "Select the visa you currently have to live in England"
        errors:
          inclusion: "You must select the visa you currently have to live in England"
      entry_date:
        question: "Enter the date you moved to England to start your teaching job"
        errors:
          presence: "Enter your entry date"
          date_not_in_future: "Date of entry cannot be in the future"
      nationality:
        question: "Select your nationality"
        errors:
          inclusion: "Choose your nationality"
      passport_number:
        question: "Enter your passport number, as it appears on your passport"
        errors:
          presence: "Enter your passport number"
          invalid: "Invalid passport number"
      current_school:
        questions:
          current_school_search: "Which school are you currently employed to teach at?"
          current_school_results: "Which school are you currently employed to teach at?"
      headteacher_details:
        questions:
          school_headteacher_name: "Enter the name of the headteacher of the school where you are employed as a teacher"
        errors:
          school_headteacher_name: "Enter the headteacher's name"
      personal_details:
        errors:
          over_max_age: Age must be below 80
          below_min_age: Age must be above 21
    check_your_answers:
      part_one:
        primary_heading: "Check your answers"
        eligibility_details: "Eligibility details"
        confirmation_notice:
          "By selecting continue you are confirming that, to the best of your knowledge, the details you are providing
          are correct."
  international_relocation_payments:
    <<: *get_a_teacher_relocation_payment
    policy_short_name: "International Relocation Payments"
    policy_acronym: "IRP"
    admin:
      decision:
        rejected_reasons:
          duplicate: Duplicate application
          previous_payment_not_received: "Has not received first year payment"
          one_non_statutory_break: "Has taken at least one non-statutory break"
          ineligible_visa: "Ineligible visa"
          ineligible_school: Ineligible school
          invalid_bank_details: Invalid bank details
          ineligible_employment_terms: Ineligible employment terms
          no_response_from_school: No response from school
          suspected_fraud: Suspected fraud
          information_mismatch_new_details_needed: "Information mismatch - new details needed"
      eligibility_answers:
        nationality: "Nationality"
        passport_number: "Passport number"
        subject: "Subject"
        school_headteacher_name: "School headteacher name"
        start_date: "Contract start date"
        visa_type: "Visa type"
        date_of_entry: "Date of entry"
      tasks:
        identity_confirmation:
          title: Verify claimants’ identity
      task_questions:
        first_year_application:
          title: "Did the claimant receive their first payment for the 2024 to 2025 academic year?"
        previous_payment:
          title: The claimant has not received an IRP payment in AY 2023/24?
        previous_residency:
          title: Does the claimant meet previous residency rules?
          hint: asd
        matching_details:
          title: "Is this claim still valid despite having matching details with other claims?"
        identity_confirmation:
          title: Have you verified the claimants’ identity?
        visa:
          title: "Is the claimant’s visa type eligible for a claim?"
        arrival_date:
          title: Has the claimant arrived in the UK within 3 months of contract start date?
        employment:
          title: "Have you confirmed with the claimant’s current employer that the details in their application are correct?"
        employment_contract:
          title: "Does the claimant’s employment contract match the above information from their claim?"
        employment_start:
          title: "Does the claimant’s employment start date match the above information from their claim?"
        employment_history:
          title: "Have you checked the claimant‘s employment history with their previous employers?"
        subject:
          title: "Does the claimant’s subject match the above information from their claim?"
        teaching_hours:
          title: "Does the teacher meet the minimum 50% teaching time requirement in their role?"
        payroll_details:
          title: "The claimant’s personal bank account details have not been automatically validated. Has the claimant confirmed their personal bank account details?"
        continuous_employment:
          title: Has the claimant had any breaks in employment during the last 3 academic terms?
